Contact

moazyusuf1998@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muaazyusuf-408140160 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Deep Learning
Full-Stack Development
Computer Vision

Languages

Arabic (Native or Bilingual) German (Limited Working) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Improving Deep Neural Networks:
Hyperparameter tuning,
Regularization and Optimization
Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Muaaz Yusuf

Computer Vision Engineer New Cairo

Summary

Self-motivated diligent with high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for deadlines. In both my academic and professional life, I have been consistently praised as diligent by professors and peers. Whether working on academic, extracurricular or professional projects, I apply proven multitasking, problem-solving and creative thinking skills.

Experience

Blessings Company
Web Developer
January 2019 - Present (3 years)
Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Freelance, self-employed Full Stack Web Developer January 2018 - Present (4 years)

Technocolabs
Computer Vision Intern
March 2021 - May 2021 (3 months)

Karizma Shop Manager June 2018 - January 2019 (8 months) Cairo Governorate, Egypt

FRESH ELECTRIC FOR HOME APPLIANCES
Customer Service Representative
April 2018 - June 2018 (3 months)
Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Education

Faculty of Computers and AI, Helwan's University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (September 2017 - July 2021)